{
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What does TCP stand for?",
      "answer": "Transmission Control Protocol.",
      "modificationDate": "2022-12-15T10:30:00Z",
      "status": "Noted"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Define UDP.",
      "answer": "User Datagram Protocol is a connectionless protocol without error checking.",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-14T09:45:00Z",
      "status": "Learned"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What is the main difference between TCP and UDP?",
      "answer": "TCP provides reliable, ordered, and error-checked delivery of data, while UDP does not guarantee delivery and is faster.",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-13T14:00:00Z",
      "status": "Want to Learn"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What does TCP use to guarantee reliable data transmission?",
      "answer": "TCP uses sequencing, acknowledgments, and retransmissions to ensure reliable data delivery.",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-12T11:20:00Z",
      "status": "Learned"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "How does UDP differ from TCP in terms of overhead?",
      "answer": "UDP has less overhead because it lacks features like sequencing, acknowledgment, and error-checking mechanisms present in TCP.",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-11T08:30:00Z",
      "status": "Noted"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which protocol is better suited for real-time applications like video streaming, TCP or UDP?",
      "answer": "UDP is often preferred due to its lower latency and faster transmission, suitable for real-time applications.",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-10T15:45:00Z",
      "status": "Learned"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Does TCP or UDP provide more robust error handling?",
      "answer": "TCP provides more robust error handling through its acknowledgment and retransmission mechanisms.",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-16T10:00:02Z",
      "status": "Noted"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "In TCP, how are out-of-order segments handled?",
      "answer": "TCP reorders out-of-order segments before delivering them to the application layer.",
      "modificationDate": "2021-10-09T10:00:02Z",
      "status": "Learned"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What type of applications might benefit from using UDP over TCP?",
      "answer": "Applications that prioritize speed and can tolerate occasional data loss, such as online multiplayer games or real-time audio/video conferencing, may benefit from UDP.",
      "modificationDate": "2022-11-14T10:00:02Z",
      "status": "Want to Learn"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What is PDU?",
      "status": "Learned",
      "answer": "Protocol Data Unit",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-18T15:29:58.003Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "What is OSI?",
      "status": "Noted",
      "answer": "Open Systems Interconnection",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-18T15:38:43.608Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "What is IP",
      "status": "Learned",
      "answer": "Internet Protocol",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-18T15:51:52.024Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "How many layers do OSI have?",
      "status": "Learned",
      "answer": "7",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-18T19:17:49.166Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "How many layers do TCP/IP have?",
      "status": "Noted",
      "answer": "4",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-18T19:22:34.212Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "3rd Layer in TCP/IP",
      "status": "Learned",
      "answer": "Internet ",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-19T05:56:36.999Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Which layer device the Router is?",
      "status": "Learned",
      "answer": "3",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-20T05:11:21.211Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Which layer device the Switch is?",
      "status": "Noted",
      "answer": "Could be 2 or 3",
      "modificationDate": "2023-12-20T05:55:54.668Z"
    }
  ]
}
